centriohost.com 2010-12-22

# Privacy Policy - CENTRIO HOST ™ - Reseller Hosting - Web Hosting Provider - Master Reseller Hosting

> **Introduction  
> ** We Centrio Hosting Service, Inc. are committed to protecting any data that we collect concerning you.  By using our services you agree to the use of the data that we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 
> 
> **We are committed to protecting your privacy  
> ** We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service. This Policy indicates the type of processes that may result in data being collected about you. Your use of this website gives us the right to collect that information. 
> 
> **Information Collected  
> ** We may collect any or all of the information that you give us depending on the type of transaction you enter into, including your name, address, telephone number, fax number and email address, together with data about your use of the website.  Other information that may be needed from time to time to process a request may also be collected as indicated on the website. 
> 
> **Information Use  
> ** We use the information collected primarily to process the task for which you visited the website. All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorized access to this information.  This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details. Centrio™ may email its monthly newsletter to the primary contact e-mail on file, but customers are able to opt out of this newsletter at any time. 
> 
> **Cookies  
> ** Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small files - "cookies" - that hold information which allows a website to recognize your account.  Our website takes advantage of this facility to enhance your experience. You have the ability to prevent your computer from accepting cookies but, if you do, certain functionality on the website may be impaired.
> 
>  **Disclosing Information  
> ** We do not disclose any personal information obtained about you from this website to third parties.  We may use the information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with our business. You will be given the opportunity to remove yourself from any mailing list or similar device. If at any time in the future we should wish to disclose information collected on this website to any third party, it would only be with your knowledge and consent. 
> 
> We may from time to time provide information of a general nature to third parties - for example, the number of individuals visiting our website or completing a registration form, but we will not use any information that could identify those individuals. 
> 
> **Disclosure to Law Enforcement  
> ** Centrio™ may disclose any subscriber information to law enforcement agencies without further consent or notification to the subscriber upon lawful request from such agencies. We will cooperate fully with law enforcement agencies.
> 
>  **Abuse Reports**  
>  We know for having lots of scam and fraudulent activities, most of the hosted customers face several unconscious abuse report(s). We therefore, tried to create a powerful abuse team to verify the abuse reports (Copyright, Email Spam, Unauthorized Activities) sent to us. We first verify the reporters identity and then verify the existence of copyrighted material according to our company law. A reporter has to send a paper with the company header signed by him/her/company's MD to prove the copyright authorization. According to MLA, only Abuse Department (Or Piracy Department) of the related company/personal is only allowed to send an abuse request to our Department for verification. If its a personal copyright, then a Passport identity including his/her copyright over the material has to be proven to our abuse department. All the documents are verified according to our law and MLA. If Abuse passes the request to Support, then support department asks the owner to take proper action against the complaint. If support doesn't receive proper information(s) from client then a suspension is issued after 15 days of escalation. This steps are only taken to prevent fraudulent scam reports and reduce the activities of support to verify the abuse report. For Email spamming a proper header is required so that its possible to do a network scan and find out the verification of the email sender.
> 
>  **Changes to this Policy  
> ** Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval. 
> 
> **Contacting Us  
> ** If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please send e-mail to : **support** [a] **centriohost.com**.  You can also correct any factual errors in that information or require us to remove your details from any list under our control.
